{"test_questions": [[{"question": "For specific antigen recognition by T cells,", "opta": "antigen is bound by a T cell membrane antibody", "optb": "denaturation of antigen does not reduce epitope recognition", "optc": "MHC molecules are not required", "optd": "antigen exposure during T cell maturation is required", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Antigen, when injected in the body activates its specific lymphocytes in the", "opta": "blood circulation", "optb": "draining lymph nodes", "optc": "MALT (mucosa associated", "optd": "spleen lymphoid tissue", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A molecule that can be covalently linked to a non-immunogenic antigen to make it an immunogen is called a (n)", "opta": "adjuvant", "optb": "carrier", "optc": "hapten", "optd": "mitogen", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is incorrect with regard to antigen epitopes?", "opta": "An epitope may be shared by two different antigens", "optb": "A protein molecule usually contains multiple epitopes", "optc": "B cells bind only processed antigen epitopes", "optd": "Epitopes may be linear or assembled", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Very low doses of antigen may induce", "opta": "hypersensitivity", "optb": "immunological ignorance", "optc": "low zone tolerance", "optd": "low zone immunity", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "During the lag period between antigen contact and detection of adaptive immunity,", "opta": "antigen is hidden from the immune system in macrophages", "optb": "innate immune effectors are eliminating antigen", "optc": "innate immunity blocks the activation of adaptive immune effector cells", "optd": "new B and T cells with the appropriate antigen specificity must be produced in the bone marrow", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Lymphocytes are activated by antigen in the", "opta": "blood stream", "optb": "bone marrow", "optc": "liver", "optd": "lymph nodes", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A pathogen can be a (n)", "opta": "agent that causes a disease", "optb": "virus", "optc": "bacteria", "optd": "All of these", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CD antigens", "opta": "allow leukocytes to recognize antigen", "optb": "are each expressed on only one cell type", "optc": "are expressed on immune cells to mark them for separation", "optd": "function as receptors for cytokine and CAMs", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A virus vaccine that can activate cytotoxic T cells must contain", "opta": "a high dose of virus particles", "optb": "an adjuvant to stimulate T cell division", "optc": "live virus", "optd": "virus peptides", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ability of an antigen to induce an immune response does not depend on the antigen's", "opta": "ability to enter the thyroid", "optb": "degree of aggregation", "optc": "dose", "optd": "size", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The antibiotic penicillin is a small molecule that does not induce antibody formation. However, penicillin binds to serum proteins and forms a complex that in some people induces antibody formation resulting in an allergic reaction. Penicillin is therefore", "opta": "an antigen", "optb": "a hapten", "optc": "an immunogen", "optd": "both an antigen and a hapten", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}